Rockwell Kent
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Alphabetical Files, circa 1900-1971, undated, Series 1:; (Reels 5153-5249, 5256, 5740-5741)
  - Einstein, Albert, 1953 (Reel 5176, Frame 482-484)
  - Eiseman, Paul, 1941 (Reel 5176, Frame 489-494)
  - Eisen, Michela, 1961-1966 (Reel 5176, Frame 495-627)
  - The Eisenhower Foundation, 1956 (Reel 5176, Frame 485-488)
  - Eisenzimmer, Ike, 1969 (Reel 5176, Frame 628-631)
  - Eisler, Hilde and Gerhart, 1962-1969 (Reel 5176, Frame 632-674)
  - Fred Eldean Organizations Incorporated, 1948 (Reel 5176, Frame 675-678)
  - Electrolux Corporation, 1946 (Reel 5176, Frame 679-681)
  - Elliott, John, 1955 (Reel 5176, Frame 682-685)
  - Ellis, Ethel, 1965 (Reel 5176, Frame 686-689)
  - Ellis, Fred, 1958, 1960 (Reel 5176, Frame 690-697)
  - Ellis, Dr. Robert H., 1959-1960 (Reel 5176, Frame 698-705)
  - Ellison, Jerome, 1940-1941 (Reel 5176, Frame 706-717)
  - Elman, Mrs. Philip, 1959 (Reel 5176, Frame 718-720)
  - Elowitz, Gertrude, and Al Moss (see also: Moss, Al, and Gertrude Elowitz), 1951-1954 (Reel 5176, Frame 721-808)
  - Elwert, Philip F., 1969 (Reel 5176, Frame 809-812)
  - Elwyn, Betty, undated (Reel 5176, Frame 813-815)
  - Elwyn, Frances H., 1941 (Reel 5176, Frame 816-820)
  - Embassies, 1948-1956, 1959-1970 (Reel 5176, Frame 821-1250)
    (invitations, correspondence about exhibitions and cultural events)
  - Embassy of the USSR, 1941-1947, undated (Reel 5176, Frame 1251-1430)
    (printed matter about art and culture; invitations to participate in conferences; invitations to receptions and social events; Artists for Victory; translations of Kent's books; loans of paintings and prints for exhibitions abroad; travel plans and passport case)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1957-1967 (Reel 5176, Frame 1431-1564)
    (printed matter; letter of appointment to executive committee; request for medal designed by Kent; discussion of the organization's publications and activities; plans for an art exhibition; Kent's legal costs for passport lawsuit)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, cont. (Reel 5177, Frame 2-392)
  - Emergency Committee to Stop Deportations to the Sahara Desert, 1941 (Reel 5177, Frame 393-395)
  - Emergency Rescue Committee, 1940-1942 (Reel 5177, Frame 396-440)
    (requests for assistance, letters of introduction, etc., for artists and writers fleeing Nazi Europe; see also: Heilbut, Ivan)
  - Employees, 1936, 1942-1970 (Reel 5177, Frame unfilmed)
    (correspondence concerning hiring of domestic, farm, and dairy workers; letters of recommendation; taxes; also, letters from former employees with news of their current lives)
  - Emspeak, Mr., 1953 (Reel 5177, Frame 441-443)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1945-1946, 1961 (Reel 5177, Frame 444-460)
  - Endicott, Mary A. and James, 1951, 1961 (Reel 5177, Frame 461-466)
  - Engebretson, Ruth (Mrs. Olaf Engebretson), 1956-1957 (Reel 5177, Frame 467-471)
  - Engel, Harry, undated (Reel 5177, Frame 472-475)
  - English Book Shop (Helen Lowry), 1930-1931 (Reel 5177, Frame 476-509)
    (correspondence regarding Kent exhibition, with list of loans; book orders)
  - Ennis, Col. Arthur I., 1942 (Reel 5177, Frame 510-512)
  - The Equitable Trust Company of New York, 1926-1931 (Reel 5177, Frame unfilmed)
    (statements of investments)
  - Erbough, Ralph, 1926 (Reel 5177, Frame 513-515)
  - Erhardt, Elisabeth, 1955 (Reel 5177, Frame 516-519)
  - Erickson, R. J., 1941 (Reel 5177, Frame 520-525)
  - Erickson, Ruth, and Eleanor Stevenson (see also: Stevenson, Eleanor, and Ruth Erickson), undated, 1952, 1961-1969 (Reel 5177, Frame 526-562)
  - Ernst, Morris (Greenbaum, Wolf & Ernst), 1931, 1934-1940 (Reel 5177, Frame 563-672)
    (concerning legal actions, mainly regarding disputes with publishers)
  - Ervin, Fred M., 1925 (Reel 5177, Frame 673-675)
  - Erwin, James William, 1952 (Reel 5177, Frame 676-741)
    (about production of rubber stamps for Kent's air mail peace stamp; Erwin's financial plan for contemporary art purchases; and ideas for collectors' Christmas peace plate)
  - Esquire, 1935-1936, 1942 (Reel 5177, Frame 742-763)
    (correspondence about commission for card to accompany Christmas gift subscriptions)
  - Essex County (N.Y.) Chamber of Commerce, 1941 (Reel 5177, Frame 764-769)
  - Essex County (N.Y.) Clerk's Office, 1949 (Reel 5177, Frame 770-772)
  - Essex County (N.Y.) Democratic Committee (see also: Democratic Committee of Essex Co.), 1968 (Reel 5177, Frame 773-776)
  - Essex County (N.Y.) Politics (see: County Politics) (Reel 5177)
  - The Essex County Republican, 1952 (Reel 5177, Frame 777-780)
  - Estey Organ Company, 1945 (Reel 5177, Frame 781-783)
  - Esto Publishing Company, 1933-1934, 1942 (Reel 5177, Frame 784-874)
    (concerning booklet on woodcuts by Kent, commissioned as part of its "Enjoy Your Museum" series, with samples of other titles in the series; Kent's text; contract and royalty statements)
  - Etnier, Stephen, 1946, 1954, 1969 (Reel 5177, Frame 875-881)
    (exhibition catalogs)
  - European Trip, 1962 (Reel 5177, Frame 882-993)
  - Euthanasia Society of America, Inc., 1941 (Reel 5177, Frame 994-996)
  - Evans, Margaret, 1947 (Reel 5177, Frame 997-1000)
  - Evans, Robert, 1943, 1946, 1948 (Reel 5177, Frame 1003-1012)
  - Evergood, Philip, undated, 1960-1961 (Reel 5177, Frame 1013-1033)
  - Eviriti, Luis F., 1970 (Reel 5177, Frame 1034-1036)
  - Ewen, Dr. Sol J., 1948 (Reel 5177, Frame 1037-1042)
  - Ewing, Blaine, 1947 (Reel 5177, Frame 1044-1046)
  - Exeter Manufacturing Company, 1947 (Reel 5177, Frame 1050-1052)
  - Exhibition Correspondence, 1926-1971 (Reel 5177, Frame 1053-1561)
    (correspondence with museums and dealers concerning details of arrangements for exhibitions, notification of sales, shipping lists, etc., includes shows at: Nebraska Art Association, 1929; Art Association of New Orleans, 1929; Toledo Museum, 1937; Cranbrook Academy, 1938; Wildenstein Galleries, 1942; Carnegie Institute, 1943; Farnsworth Museum, 1950; Moscow Exhibition, 1957; Colby College, 1962; see also: W. S. Budworth & Son)
  - Exhibition Correspondence, cont. (Reel 5178, Frame 2-178)
  - Exhibitions (Rockwell Kent), undated, 1903-1959 (Reel 5178, Frame 179-320)
    (announcements, invitations, and catalogs for solo exhibitions and group shows)
  - Exhibitions (other artists), undated, 1920-1959 (Reel 5178, Frame unfilmed)
    (exhibition prospecti and entry blanks; announcements, invitations, and catalogs of other artists' shows; also, bulletins and general publications of museums and arts organizations)
  - Expense Sheets, Travel, etc., 1932-1966 (Reel 5178, Frame unfilmed)
    (receipts and itineraries)
  - The Explorers Club, 1941-1959 (Reel 5178, Frame 321-363)
  - E, Unidentified (Reel 5178, Frame 364-367)
    (Betty E., 1945; Dee Dee, 1969)
  - Faber & Faber, Ltd., Publishers (F. V. Horley), 1936 (Reel 5178, Frame 368-379)
    (correspondence about publication of Kent's books in England)
  - Fabian, Mr., 1952 (Reel 5178, Frame 380-382)
  - Factory Point National Bank, 1922-1924 (Reel 5178, Frame unfilmed)
    (canceled checks and account statement)
  - Fadden, Alfred and Roz, 1970 (Reel 5178, Frame 383-396)
  - Fagan, Vincent and William Goodwin, 1944-1949 (Reel 5178, Frame 397-581)
    (correspondence about ancient Norse ruins in North America; politics and Catholicism)
  - Fahnestock, Karol, 1950-1951 (Reel 5178, Frame 582-592)
  - Fairview Association, 1956 (Reel 5178, Frame 594-595)
  - Family (of Sally [Shirley Johnstone] Kent), 1952-1970 (Reel 5178, Frame 596-1391)
    (correspondence with parents and assorted relatives, including: family news, the Kents' trips abroad, and Estate of Aunt Netta [Benetta Johnstone])
  - Fan Mail, undated, 1907-1971 (Reel 5178, Frame 1392-1571)
    (letters about Kent's art, writings, and politics, with frequent requests for autographs, photographs, and advice, with some replies from Kent; also fan letters from Kent to others in praise of their service, ideas, and work)
  - Fan Mail, cont. (Reel 5179, Frame 2-1556)
  - Fan Mail, cont. (Reel 5180, Frame 1-1583)
  - Fan Mail, cont. (Reel 5181, Frame 2-652)
  - Farm, 1943-1970 (Reel 5181, Frame unfilmed)
    (routine correspondence and bills; printed matter from New York Department of Agriculture and agriculture associations; cattle registration)
  - Farm Research, 1941 (Reel 5181, Frame 653-663)
  - Farmers' Educational and Cooperative Union of America, 1947-1951 (Reel 5181, Frame 664-681)
    (correspondence about political activities and controversy over Iowa leadership)
  - Farmers' Union of the New York Milk Shed, 1942-1952 (Reel 5181, Frame 682-711)
  - Farnsworth, Dan, undated, 1950 (Reel 5181, Frame 712-716)
  - Farnsworth, Kicki (Mrs. Robert P. Farnsworth), 1941-1945 (Reel 5181, Frame 717-737)
  - Farrar & Rinehart, Inc., 1931-1939 (Reel 5181, Frame 741-749)
    (concerning commissions for book illustrations and cover designs)
  - Farrar, John, 1927 (Reel 5181, Frame 738-740)
  - Farrar, Straus and Company, Incorporated, undated (Reel 5181, Frame 750-752)
  - Farrell, Isabella, 1945 (Reel 5181, Frame 753-755)
  - Fast, Francis, undated (Reel 5181, Frame 756-759)
  - Fast, Howard, 1950-1955 (Reel 5181, Frame 760-796)
    (correspondence about book illustration and promotion of Fast's books; activities of various pacifist organizations)
  - Fastholm, Jorgen, 1950 (Reel 5181, Frame 797-801)
  - Faulkner, Barry, 1908 (Reel 5181, Frame 802-810)
  - Faulkner, Ray, 1941 (Reel 5181, Frame 811-815)
  - Faulkner, William, 1965 (Reel 5181, Frame 816-819)
    (correspondence with biographer about Faulkner)
  - Faven, Mauri, 1959-1960 (Reel 5181, Frame 820-824)
  - Fay, Margaret Elsie, 1956-1957, 1968 (Reel 5181, Frame 825-840)
  - Federal Arts Project, Works Progress Administration, 1936-1939 (Reel 5181, Frame 841-954)
    (letters to the president and other elected officials urging support of federal fine arts legislation; printed matter of Union of Professional Workers of America; correspondence with Kent outlining strategies for lobbying; see also: WPA Miscellaneous)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1941, 1946 (Reel 5181, Frame 955-959)
  - Federal Fine Arts Department, 1940 (Reel 5181, Frame 960-1033)
  - Federal Union, 1942 (Reel 5181, Frame 1034-1037)
  - Federal Works Agency, United States Housing Authority, 1941 (Reel 5181, Frame 1038-1041)
  - Federal Writers' Project, Works Progress Administration, 1938-1939 (Reel 5181, Frame 1042-1080)
    (correspondence and printed matter; Kent's comments on poor design and printing of some of its projects; see also: WPA Miscellaneous)
  - Federation for Constitutional Rights, 1941 (Reel 5181, Frame 1081-1084)
  - Federation of Jewish Charities, 1942-1943 (Reel 5181, Frame 1085-1089)
  - Feek, Isabel (Mrs. Dwight Lyman Feek), undated (Reel 5181, Frame 1090-1092)
  - Feild, Robin (Robert), 1950-1951, undated (Reel 5181, Frame 1093-1248)
    (correspondence about modernism, and the role of art and the artist in economic and cultural revolution; plans to write a book together, with partial manuscript on their philosophy of art as the expression of human experience; professional intimidation of Feild for his political ideas)
  - Feild-Kent Manuscript, circa 1950-1952 (Reel 5181, Frame 1249-1268)
  - Fejes, Claire, 1959-1971 (Reel 5181, Frame 1269-1374)
  - Fence Dispute (see also: Cowdin, Cheever and Katherine), 1957-1959 (Reel 5181, Frame unfilmed)
  - Fencing Agreements, 1957-1958 (Reel 5181, Frame unfilmed)
  - Fendley, Francis, 1941-1946 (Reel 5181, Frame 1375-1383)
  - Fernandez, Pablo, 1939-1941, undated (Reel 5181, Frame unfilmed)
    (letters, drawings, and schoolwork of Spanish foster child; see also: Foster Parents' Plan)
  - Feuchtwanger, Lion and Harta, 1955-1959 (Reel 5181, Frame 1384-1393)
  - Field, Earl, 1958 (Reel 5181, Frame 1394-1398)
  - Eugene Field Society, 1941 (Reel 5181, Frame 1399-1401)
  - Fifth Amendment Statement and Questionnaire, 1953-1954 (Reel 5181, Frame 1402-1441)
  - Fifth Ave. Bank of N.Y., 1921-1922 (Reel 5181, Frame unfilmed)
    (account statements and canceled checks)
  - Fifty Famous American Paintings, 1940 (Reel 5181, Frame 1442-1470)
    (lists of best contemporary American artists, and questionnaire developed by Kent and Carl Zigrosser for Living American Art, Inc.; plan for mail order marketing of reproductions; see also: Living American Art, Inc.)
  - Fifty Print Show, 1925-1928 (Reel 5181, Frame 1471-1524)
    (correspondence concerning the administrative details of selecting works and writing catalogs for Fifty Prints of the Year exhibitions)
  - Fight for Freedom, Inc., 1941 (Reel 5181, Frame 1525-1532)
  - Films for Democracy, 1939 (Reel 5181, Frame 1533-1537)
  - Findley, Maida, 1941 (Reel 5181, Frame 1538-1545)
  - Finkelstein, C., 1949 (Reel 5181, Frame 1546-1552)
  - Finkelstein, Sidney (Vanguard Recording Society), 1955-1970 (Reel 5181, Frame 1553-1575)
    (correspondence regarding record cover designs, music and musicians; books by Kent, Finkelstein, and Irene Downes; Kent's Moscow exhibition and passport lawsuit; see also: Vanguard Recording Society)
  - Finkelstein, Sidney (Vanguard Recording Society), cont. (Reel 5182, Frame 2-111)
  - Finney, Kathleen Kent [daughter] and Peter, 1937-1971 (Reel 5182, Frame 112-1541)
    (family news; divorce and protracted attempts to recover alimony and child support payments; Kathleen's and her mother's health; financial problems and employment; children's schooling; letters and drawings by her children; see also: Kent, Kathleen)
  - Finnish Hall, Inc., 1941 (Reel 5182, Frame 1542-1546)
  - Fire, 1969 (Reel 5183, Frame 3-339)
  - Fire and Pumpkin Broadcast, 1948-1949 (Reel 5182, Frame 1547-1580)
    (letters of congratulations on Kent's Christmas broadcast; letters of thanks for lithograph given as Christmas gifts)
  - Fischel, Lillian, 1941 (Reel 5183, Frame 340-347)
  - Carl Fischer Musical Instrument Co., Inc., 1951-1952 (Reel 5183, Frame 348-352)
  - Fishing Rights, 1941-1942 (Reel 5183, Frame unfilmed)
    (correspondence and legal documents concerning purchase of federal landbank easements)
  - Fisk University, 1944-1960 (Reel 5183, Frame 353-383)
    (correspondence about gifts of prints and painting to the university; invitation to participate in a seminar on art and music)
  - FitzGerald, Chuck, 1967 (Reel 5183, Frame 384-387)
  - Fitzgerald, Gerald, 1945 (Reel 5183, Frame 388-391)
  - Fitzgerald, James, 1953-1970 (Reel 5183, Frame 392-593)
    (correspondence about family, mutual friends, and Kent house on Monhegan; see also: Monhegan)
  - FitzGerald, Jean, 1965 (Reel 5183, Frame 594-598)
  - Flannagan, Margharita, 1942 (Reel 5183, Frame 599-603)
  - Fleming Museum Art Association, 1938 (Reel 5183, Frame 604-606)
  - Fles, Bartold, 1965-1970 (Reel 5183, Frame 617-705)
  - Flint, S. L., 1948 (Reel 5183, Frame 607-609)
  - The Florida Sportsman, 1946 (Reel 5183, Frame 610-612)
  - Florsheim, Richard A., 1955 (Reel 5183, Frame 613-616)
  - Floyd Bennett Field Murals, 1940 (Reel 5183, Frame 706-779)
    (clippings about WPA murals by August Henkel and Eugene Chodorow destroyed because of alleged Communist content, with letters of protest and plans for organizing public demonstrations; see also: "Hate" Mail)
  - Flynn, Elizabeth Curley, 1950 (Reel 5183, Frame 780-782)
  - Folensbee, Bradley J., Jr., 1955-1964 (Reel 5183, Frame 783-807)
  - Foley, Marion Riggs, undated, 1960-1961 (Reel 5183, Frame 815-825)
  - Foner, Mrs., 1953 (Reel 5183, Frame 826-828)
  - Foner, Philip S., 1966 (Reel 5183, Frame 829-832)
  - Forbes, John Ripley, 1945 (Reel 5183, Frame 833-842)
  - Forbes, Juliette E., 1965 (Reel 5183, Frame 843-846)
  - Forbes, Rev. Kenneth Ripley, 1953-1965 (Reel 5183, Frame 847-865)
  - Ford, Julia Ellsworth, 1944 (Reel 5183, Frame 877-880)
  - The Ford Foundation, 1959 (Reel 5183, Frame 866-872)
  - Ford Hall Forum, 1942 (Reel 5183, Frame 873-876)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1954 (Reel 5183, Frame 881-883)
  - Foreign Correspondents Dinner-Forum, 1941 (Reel 5183, Frame 808-814)
  - Foreign Editions of Rockwell Kent Works, 1937, 1946-1969 (Reel 5183, Frame 884-1096)
    (correspondence about copyrights and reproduction permissions)
  - Foreman, Clark and Mairi, 1957-1971 (Reel 5183, Frame 1097-1169)
  - The Forest Preserve Association of New York State, 1941 (Reel 5183, Frame 1170-1174)
  - Form Letters (Reel 5183, Frame 1175-1194)
    (used by dairy; also, for standard replies to fan mail)
  - Fort Hamilton High School, 1942 (Reel 5183, Frame 1195-1198)
  - Fort Worth Art Center, 1965 (Reel 5183, Frame 1199-1202)
  - Fortune, 1942-1943 (Reel 5183, Frame 1203-1213)
  - Fossum, Syd and Bunny, 1942-1943, 1960-1970 (Reel 5183, Frame 1214-1255)
  - Foster, Barbara, 1936-1938 (Reel 5183, Frame 1256-1280)
    (correspondence with and about psychiatric patient boarding with the Kents; manuscript of novel by Foster [ms. not filmed])
  - Foster, Lillian Fargo, 1966 (Reel 5183, Frame 1281-1284)
  - Foster Parents' Plan (for War Children, Inc.), 1939-1940 (Reel 5183, Frame unfilmed)
    (form letters to participants; receipts for contributions; see also: Alejos, Elidea Pinto; Fernandez, Pablo)
  - Four Continent Book Corporation, 1943, 1954 (Reel 5183, Frame 1285-1289)
  - 4-H Club, 1961 (Reel 5183, Frame 1290-1292)
  - Fowler, Alfred, 1957 (Reel 5183, Frame 1293-1305)
  - Fox, Dr. Dixon Ryan, 1944 (Reel 5183, Frame 1306-1319)
  - Fractenberg, Harry, 1939, 1948 (Reel 5183, Frame 1320-1326)
  - Frampton, Mr., 1946 (Reel 5183, Frame 1327-1329)
  - France, Clemens J., 1952 (Reel 5183, Frame 1330-1333)
  - France, Royal W. and Ruth, 1957-1966 (Reel 5183, Frame 1334-1450)
  - Frane, Sydney, 1955 (Reel 5183, Frame 1451-1454)
  - Frankfort Distilleries, Incorporated, 1942 (Reel 5183, Frame 1455-1459)
  - Frantz, Ruth Chappell, 1953 (Reel 5183, Frame 1460-1465)
  - Fraternal Outlook, 1948, undated (Reel 5183, Frame 1466-1564)
    (articles and texts of radio speeches on labor, Ukrainian Folk Festival, economy, and presidential election)
  - Fraternal Outlook, cont. (Reel 5184, Frame 2-21)
  - Fraternity of Phi Gamma Delta (see also: Phi Gamma Delta), 1941, 1945, 1955 (Reel 5184, Frame 22-35)
  - Fredenburgh, Theodore, 1938 (Reel 5184, Frame 36-38)
  - Free Denmark, Inc., 1941 (Reel 5184, Frame 39-45)
  - Free Work, 1943-1947, 1959-1960 (Reel 5184, Frame 46-241)
    (correspondence about drawings donated to various causes for their publications or fund-raising efforts; see also: Causes; Charities; Contributions; Gifts, Helpees)
  - Free World Association, 1941 (Reel 5184, Frame 242-244)
  - Freedman, Ruth, 1930 (Reel 5184, Frame 245-249)
  - Freedom of the Press Co., Inc., 1942 (Reel 5184, Frame 250-252)
  - The Freeman, 1954 (Reel 5184, Frame 253-255)
  - Freeman, Bernard, 1941 (Reel 5184, Frame 256-259)
  - Freeman, Fred, 1955 (Reel 5184, Frame 260-264)
  - Freeman, Harry and Vera, 1959-1970 (Reel 5184, Frame 265-286)
  - French, George F., 1924 (Reel 5184, Frame 287-289)
  - Freuchen, Peter and Magda, 1929-1945; Peter and Dagmar, 1945-1957 (Reel 5184, Frame 290-866)
    (correspondence about Freuchen's and Kent's writings, reviews and translations; Freuchen on trip to the Arctic, USSR, and South America; news of family and mutual friends; biographical notes on Freuchen; Freuchen's experiences in Hollywood and shooting commercial films in Alaska; opening of air routes to Greenland; lecture itineraries; effect of World War II on Denmark; divorce and remarriage, with detailed plans for wedding at Asgaard; national and international politics, including 1948 Wallace campaign and labor movement; helping friends find publishers; clippings and photographs)
  - Friday, Inc., 1940 (Reel 5184, Frame 867-869)
  - Friedman, Arnold, 1945 (Reel 5184, Frame 870-874)
  - Friel, Edward, 1956-1957 (Reel 5184, Frame 875-939)
    (Kent's comments about Friel's article on color theory, with copy of Friel's letter to Arthur U. Pope)
  - Friel, J. Whiting, 1952, 1957 (Reel 5184, Frame 940-951)
  - Friends of Democracy, Inc., 1941 (Reel 5184, Frame 952-961)
  - Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade (see also: Abraham Lincoln Brigade), 1938 (Reel 5184, Frame 962-966)
  - Friends Service Committee, 1957 (Reel 5184, Frame 967-969)
  - Friendship House (Union of Soviet Societies for Friendship and Cultural Exchange with Foreign Countries), 1960 (Reel 5184, Frame 970-994)
    (correspondence about exhibition and gift of Kent paintings to the organization; see also: Gift Correspondence; and Kent Collection)
  - Friendship Societies, 1962-1969 (Reel 5184, Frame 995-1094)
  - Fritchman, Rev. Stephen (First United Methodist Church, Los Angeles, Calif.), 1948-1961 (Reel 5184, Frame 1095-1166)
    (correspondence about pacifist activities, world politics and their experiences with House Un-American Activities Committee; news of family and mutual friends; donation of Kent prints for church fund raising)
  - Froelich, Ludwig W., 1941-1970 (Reel 5184, Frame 1167-1371)
    (correspondence about advertising work with detailed discussion of technical aspects of printing; Kent collectors; publication of Kent portfolio)
  - Fuel Coupons, 1943-1945 (Reel 5184, Frame unfilmed)
    (see also: Rationing Correspondence)
  - Fuess, Claude M., 1936 (Reel 5184, Frame 1372-1374)
  - Fuller, Ann, 1951, 1958 (Reel 5184, Frame 1375-1382)
  - Fuller, William Allison, 1939 (Reel 5184, Frame 1383-1388)
  - The Fund for the Republic, Inc., 1955-1957 (Reel 5184, Frame 1389-1402)
  - Funeral, 1971 (Reel 5184, Frame 1403-1422)
    (see also: Condolence Letters and Sympathy Cards; and Memorial Portfolio)
  - Funny Letters, 1931-1938 (Reel 5184, Frame 1423-1443)
  - Funt, Mrs., 1953 (Reel 5184, Frame 1444-1446)
  - Fur Dressers' and Dyers' Unions, 1953, 1956 (Reel 5184, Frame 1447-1453)
  - Furlong, Lt. Col. Charles Wellington, 1922, 1966-1967 (Reel 5184, Frame 1454-1463)
  - Furman, Erwin (The Print Rooms, Los Angeles, Calif.), 1954 (Reel 5184, Frame 1464-1480)
    (about exhibition and sale of Kent prints and illustrated books; correspondence about pricing; final sales report)
  - Furtseva, Ekaterina A., 1969 (Reel 5184, Frame 1481-1485)
  - Fyans, Catherine, 1947, 1949 (Reel 5184, Frame 1486-1491)
  - F, Illegible (Reel 5184, Frame 1492-1493)
    (Bill Fro[illegible], 1968)
  - Gaeth, Arthur, 1948 (Reel 5184, Frame 1494-1499)
  - Gahn, Joseph A., 1965 (Reel 5184, Frame 1500-1503)
  - Gaige, Crosby, 1928-1946 (Reel 5184, Frame 1504-1531)
    (correspondence concerning publication of Unser Kent, a poem by Waldo Peirce, illustrated by Kent; see also: Peirce, Waldo)
  - The Galesburg Civic Art League, 1942 (Reel 5184, Frame 1532-1535)
  - The Gallery of Modern Art, 1965 (Reel 5184, Frame 1536-1538)
  - Gallery of Modern Masters, 1937-1938 (Reel 5184, Frame 1539-1566)
    (arrangements for exhibition, with correspondence concerning pricing and sales)
  - Gallery of Modern Masters, cont. (Reel 5185, Frame 2-38)
  - Gallery of the Society of Beaux Arts Architects, 1911 (Reel 5185, Frame 39-43)
  - Gamble & Co. (T. S. Gamble), 1929-1930 (Reel 5185, Frame 44-95)
    (regarding advertising work)
  - The Gamut Arts Club, 1941 (Reel 5185, Frame 96-104)
  - Garber, Frederick W., 1940 (Reel 5185, Frame 105-107)
  - Garden, 1940-1944 (Reel 5185, Frame unfilmed)
    (printed matter, orders for seeds)
  - Garden City Publishing Co. (see: Shakespeare) (Reel 5185)
  - Gardner, Mary, 1955 (Reel 5185, Frame 108-114)
  - Garlin, Martha Millet, 1952 (Reel 5185, Frame 115-119)
  - Garlin, Sender, 1969 (Reel 5185, Frame 120-122)
  - Garrett, Paul, 1946 (Reel 5185, Frame 123-126)
  - Garrow, Patsy (see: Patsy [Garrow]) (Reel 5185)
  - Garso Family, 1946 (Reel 5185, Frame 127-129)
  - Gauld, Charles A., 1941 (Reel 5185, Frame 130-142)
    (correspondence about labor conditions and politics in Puerto Rico and South America)
  - Gay, Evelyn, 1959-1960 (Reel 5185, Frame 143-146)